

About Me

I developed a keen interest in the Japanese language at a young age due to my exposure to anime series. To further enhance my language skills, I enrolled in a Chinese school to learn basic Mandarin, which greatly contributed to my Kanji proficiency.

Working in the BPO industry enhanced my English and communication skills. Recently, I formalized my Japanese language learning in 2022. Now well-equipped, I seek to apply my language skills and cultural knowledge professionally.



0929 - 781 - 2182 (Smart)



falconadriel@gmail.com



Door 3 Roco Bldg, Zone 1, Igualdad Interior, Naga City, Camarines Sur.



Date of Birth: 10/07/1991 (31 years old)

Language

- English
- Japanese Language (N5) TESDA
 National Certificate

Expertise

- Communication skills
- Imaginative thinking
- Customer service
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Adaptability
- Multi-tasking
- Conflict Resolution
- Time Management

Skills Summary

Teaching Skills 98%

Digital Graphics Art 96%

BENJAMIN ADRIEL H. FALCON III.

Work Experience

Telus International Philippines | Netspend

Araneta Center, Gen. McArthur Ave., Cubao, Quezon City, Metro Manila Customer Service Representative | December 2019 - June 2020

 Handles customer service calls, billing and transaction reviews for prepaid debit cards.

Quantrics Enterprises Inc. | Bell Canada

SM BPO Bldg., Taytay Diversion Rd., Dolores, Taytay, Rizal Senior Loyalty Agent | June 2018 - June 2019

- Handled outbound and inbound loyalty calls for Canada's leading telecommunication provider.
- Dialed outbound calls for save back offers for customer retention.

Quantrics Enterprises Inc. | Bell Canada

Robinsons Place Naga, Almeda Hwy., Roxas Ave., Naga City, Camarines Sur Customer Service Representative | February 2018 - May 2018

 Assisted customers with simple to complex billing and technical concerns.

Stellar Philippines | P&O Cruises Australia

3F ANR Building, Conception Grande, Naga City, Camarines Sur Customer Cruise Specialist (Blended) | July 2016 - January 2018

- Handled inbound calls for ticket sales and reservations for cruises around Southeast Asia
- Maintained customer account records via loyalty program.

Concentrix Daksh Services Philippines | Sears Canada

2F Naga City IT Park, Ninoy and Cory Ave., Naga City, Camarines Sur Customer Service Representative | February 2015 - June 2015

Sutherland Global Services Philippines | Intuit QuickBooks

Camarines Sur IT Park, Pili City, Camarines Sur

Customer Service Representative | February 2013 - December 2014

- Managed online and phone software registration.
- Handled account maintenance, billing, and up-sell for accounting software upgrades.
- Assisted customers with minor processes and technical issues.

Education

Universidad de Sta. Isabel | Elias Angeles St., Naga City, Camarines Sur

B.S. Food Service and Institutional Management

Undergraduate (1st Year - 1st Semester) | A.Y. June - October 2012

Camarines Sur National High School | Magsaysay Ext., Naga City, Camarines Sur

Highschool Graduate | S.Y. 2010 - 2012

Hope Christian School | St. Vincent Village, Cabangan, Legazpi City Elementary Level | S.Y. 2004 - 2006

Training

Southeast Asian Institute of Computer Technology

Student of Japanese Language N4 Level | October 16, 2022 - Present With Japanese Language N5 TESDA National Certificate

Certificate





Technical Education and Skills Development Authority

SOUTHEAST ASIAN INSTITUTE
OF COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY

Present this

Certificate of Training

to

BENJAMIN ADRIEL HEMADY FALCON III

ULI: FBH-91-367-13088-001

after having successfully completed the competency requirements in

Japanese Language and Culture

CTPR No: 202205170005 Duration 180 hours

Given this 17th of March 2023 at 2nd floor, Camarines Sur Trade and Investment Center BMC ROad, Panganiban Drive, Naga City

MA JESSA L SALVADOR Registrar

W d JEREMIAS School Administrate

DANILO R CRUZ TESDA Director General

COMPETENCIES COMPLETED

Basic Competencies

Participate in Workplace Communication
Work in Team Environment
Solve/Address General Workplace Problems
Develop Career and Life Decisions
Contribute to Workplace Innovation
Present Relevant Information
Practice Occupational Safety and Health Policies and
Procedures
Exercise Efficient and Effective Sustainable Practices in the
Workplace
Practice Entrepreneurial Skills in the Workplace

Common Competencies

Apply Quality Standards Perform Computer Operations

Core Competencies

Introduce Japanese Culture and Basic Language Introduce Japanese Language Grammar Introduce Basic Japanese Kanji Characters

Scan QR Code to validate this Certificate



Actual Date of Training Start of Training: 1/6/2023 End of Training: 3/17/2023 Certificate No: 2023-05-17-003387



Japanese Language N5 TESDA National Certificate